<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Mónica Cortiñas</title>
    <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Mónica Cortiñas</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mónica Cortiñas &amp;copy; 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Competencias Digitales del Profesorado</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/digital-competencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/digital-competencies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;objetivos&#34;&gt;Objetivos&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Con este proyecto pretendemos contribuir al diagnóstico y la mejora de las &lt;strong&gt;competencias digitales&lt;/strong&gt; del profesorado en los centros de educación secundaria en Navarra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;En concreto, pretendemos colaborar respondiendo a las siguientes preguntas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- ¿Cuál es el &lt;strong&gt;grado&lt;/strong&gt; de competencia digital en los y las docentes?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- ¿Existen &lt;strong&gt;diferencias&lt;/strong&gt; por &lt;strong&gt;género&lt;/strong&gt;?, ¿y por &lt;strong&gt;edad&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- ¿Existen diferencias según el &lt;strong&gt;nivel de enseñanza&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;aportaciones&#34;&gt;Aportaciones&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Con este proyecto esperamos realizar aportaciones relevantes para tres grupos de interés de la sociedad navarra:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- El departamento de Educación del Gobierno de Navarra al poder &lt;strong&gt;adaptar la oferta formativa&lt;/strong&gt; a las necesidades concretas del profesorado y tomar decisiones en política de formación inicial y a lo largo de la carrera profesional del profesorado más acertadas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- El profesorado, &lt;strong&gt;mejorando el perfil profesional&lt;/strong&gt; de los y las docentes para la era digital y, consecuentemente,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;- Los y las estudiantes al aumentar la &lt;strong&gt;calidad de la educación&lt;/strong&gt; más acorde con la sociedad digital. Además, en este último grupo de interés se espera contribuir en el “refuerzo de las competencias digitales del alumnado” que se propone en el Plan Estratégico de Formación Profesional de Navarra (2017-2020).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Retailing</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The development of artificial intelligence is impacting heavily in fields such as the labor market, energy supply control systems, financial markets and also consumer decision-making and the way in which individuals relate to companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this project we are working on the implications of the development of artificial intelligence for marketing and retailing, especially in the field of e-commerce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual attention in e-commerce</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/eyetracking-visualattention/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/eyetracking-visualattention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this ongoing project we use eye-tracking techniques to analyze the processes of attention to the website in electronic commerce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile and traditional videogames</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/mobile-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/mobile-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this ongoing project, in which a doctoral thesis is being developed, we analyze the relationship and the differences between the consumption of video games on mobile platforms and traditional platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnichannel behavior</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/omnichannel-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/omnichannel-behavior/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The so-called omnichannel phenomenon has had an exponential growth in the last decade. In this project we explore how we can characterize it and what implications it has for retailing strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services Marketing</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/services-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/services-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project we explore the distinctive features of the services and the challenges of their commercialization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agricultural Marketing</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/agricultural-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/agricultural-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project we explore the distinctive characteristics of agri-food products and the challenges of their commercialization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retailing strategy</title>
      <link>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/retailers-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monicacortinas.net/en/project/retailers-strategy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project we explore relevant aspects for the management of services, prices, assortment and promotions in retail distribution.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
